Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/iameuna (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Maya

Photoshop

Digital Illustration

Languages

Korean (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

Finalists - BBC New Animator

Euna Kwon

Design System at Facebook

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

Professional Design System designer and UI / UX production designer with over 9 years of experience in the tech industry.

Ability to create and maintain product design components and sticker sheets and build and educate new design system process to teams.

I would love to connect.

Experience

Meta

1 year 6 months

Design system/production designer at Facebook September 2022 - Present (8 months)

Design System/Production Designer at Entertainment Org November 2021 - August 2022 (10 months)

United States

Facebook

Design System designer/Production Designer (TEKsystems on-site) July 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 5 months)

Work with brand & product design to develop Entertainment Design System.

- · Design systems and patterns that will allow product designers and frontend engineers to focus on product-level problems and ship high-quality work efficiently and consistently.
- · Provide pixel-perfect static and interactive mockups.
- · Provide guidelines and documentation that connects and resonates with the teams using Entertainment Design Systems.
- · Work with Product Designers, Software Engineers, and Content Designers to develop and ship the system.
- · Write documentation and guidance on how and why components, styles, and patterns are applied in code and design.

Page 1 of 4

· As a design system ambassador, articulate design decisions to product design, brand design, engineering, and product.

Airbnb

1 year

Production Designer
June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

UX Production Designer, Design System August 2019 - May 2020 (10 months)

San Francisco, California

Create and facilitate Airbnb's Email Design system and visual QA

Produce clear specs that advocate Airbnb's design language system and work closely with cross functional partners including product, engineering, research and QA.

Develop pixel perfect screens and localize them for global marketing and optimizing image assets for web, iOS, Android and print.

Create icons and animate them on stakeholder's demand. Document and share work processes to support other teammates.

Apple

6 years 2 months

Senior Designer @iTunes(Matthews international on-site) October 2017 - August 2019 (1 year 11 months)

iTunes marketing at Apple

Assisting Apple Music marketing team at Apple Inc. in designing icons, buttons, and high-resolution screens while adhering to brand guidelines. Support Apple Music Global team to localize US master screens. Design and create documentation for new features of Apple devices for third party retailers in worldwide.

Senior Production Lead @Marcom (Hogarth Worldwide on-site) January 2017 - October 2017 (10 months)

Image Studio at Marcom, Apple

Maintain a leadership role, facilitate and develop new production processes in creating high resolution assets, and manage incoming work to be distributed to a team of production artists. Assist in training artists in creating "pixel perfect"

UI for all Apple devices for cross functional teams that include print, video, and interactive.

Anticipate production artists needs, answer questions that may arise, and streamline productivity. Design and create documentation on Apple devices, communicate best practices, and discuss new building techniques between production artists.

Production Artist (Schawk on-site)
July 2013 - December 2016 (3 years 6 months)
Content Production Studio at Marcom, Apple

Build pixel perfect screens using vector in Photoshop for world-wide marketing purposes.

Mock up ios and osx product screen files in high resolution for interactive, video, keynote, retail and printing teams

Building master files of osx and ios to make easy and fast contents swap for GEO team

Typesetting for Korean GEO

Interactive Touch Books
Author and Illustrator
June 2012 - June 2013 (1 year 1 month)
san francisco bay area

Animal character designs and animation using provided software from interactive Touch Books.

Optical Design Compositor & video editor January 2007 - October 2008 (1 year 10 months) seoul, korea

Keyframe animation for banners on client's website in Flash
TV commercial's visual effects and animation for client's demand in After
Effects and edit the animation in Final Cut Pro also to add sounds effect
Logo and character designs for local festivals

Picasso Pictures
Compositor and Editor
August 2006 - September 2006 (2 months)
london, united kingdom

Sound and Video Editing company's showreel and TV commercial preview for clients in After Effects and Final Cut Pro

Voodoodog Animator and Compositor January 2006 - August 2006 (8 months) London, United Kingdom

Title and ending sequence animating for movies in After Effects

Chracter design and Keyframe animation for in house project in Flash

Education

Academy of Art University

Master of Fine Arts (MFA), Visual Development

Gachon University
Bachelor of Arts (BA), Fine/Studio Arts, General

University of Westminster Bachelor of Arts (BA), Animation